Yeah, no.
What?!
Anya cannot accept this mama.
You're just not going to cut it
for the mother role, Franky.
You're literally a spy. Couldn't you
have done my disguise better?
There's only so much I can do
with your height and physique.
I can't believe I volunteered for this!
Have a peanut.
Operation Strix.
In order to stop a key figure in Ostania,
Desmond, from trying to start a war,
I was given this top-secret
mission as a member of WISE.
We were able to pass the written exam to
get into the prestigious Eden College,
but who knew the interview process's next stage
demanded the attendance of both parents?
Very well.
SECURE A WIFE
I guess I'll have to explore my options.
Did you hear? A thief
might've entered our office.
Capital City Berlint, City Hall
Apparently, they only searched drawers
with information regarding the girls.
Like, what? What kind of creep does that?
Honestly, the section chief is way creepier.
He's always ogling me.
That's because you're always
wearing those short skirts.
Well, my boyfriend likes
it when I wear them.
You've got a nice figure yourself,
Sharon, so flaunt it more.
You don't bother anymore
once you have a kid.
So hey...
What do you think about this,
Yor? Isn't it creepy?
Sorry?
Is that the section chief's coffee?
Let's put some boogers in it.
Huh?
Do boogers somehow make it taste better?
You know, Yor... I've gotta
say you're rather...
unique.
I know, right?
She's so out there that I bet
guys keep their distance.
Come on, now, Millie.
You've got a nice face and body, Yor.
You'd be a knockout if you just dressed up.
Uh-huh...
I'll give you the deets on some
of my favorite cosmetics.
I'm honestly content as long
as I get to keep this job.
But aren't you, like, 27?
You need to be careful.
There seem to be a lot of spies
around lately, you know?
So people are apparently getting
reported over the tiniest things.
The other day, a single
woman in her late twenties
got reported by her neighbors
for being suspicious.
Wait, what? That's hilarious.
You know everything, Camilla.
True, it's unheard of to be single
at that age. Very suspicious.
Oh, I see. Thank you for the warning.
Oh, yeah. I'm having a party
at my place this weekend.
You should totally come, Yor.
Make sure you bring your partner with you.
Isn't that asking a bit much?
Maybe the creeper who snuck into
this place will go with her.
That's so mean!
Hello, Briar residence.
Hey, Sis. How have you been?
Oh, Yuri.
How's work going?
Don't worry. I'm still employed.
I'm worried about you.
You're kinda unusual, y'know.
How rude. I'm completely normal.
Isn't it about time you got married?
Anyone you're interested in?
This again?
The thing is, there's a chance
I might get promoted...
Meaning I'll probably be even busier
running around than before.
But I can't leave you alone like this,
so I'm not sure if I should take it.
The whole reason I got this far is
because of you, and I'm truly grateful.
That's why I just want you to be happy.
I know.
Thank you, Yuri.
If you want, I can introduce you to someone.
Huh? N-No, that's okay.
O-Oh, yes. I'm actually going
to a party this weekend.
With my partner, of course.
Huh? You have a boyfriend?
I do, actually...
So don't worry.
I see! That's great. It'll be a
party with coworkers, right?
Yup. Camilla's throwing it.
Ah.
Then I'll have to ask Dominic
about the guy later.
Huh?
I mean, I know how gullible you are.
I'll have to chase him away if he's a loser.
Huh? Um...
I'll hold off on this promotion
until I know he's a good guy.
Oh, you don't need to do tha—
I look forward to meeting him. Goodnight.
What should I do?
I need to find someone by
the time of the party.
If he finds out I'm lying, he'll think
I'm a weirdo and a pathological liar,
and he'll lose even more trust in me.
I need to find someone for the sake
of my little brother's promotion.
Yuri, you've got the wrong idea!
I was just joking earlier—
Oh, dear. Did you buddy-buddy
siblings actually have a quarrel?
Oh, Shopkeeper?
I'm sorry, I didn't realize it was you.
Good evening. I have a client
for you, Thorn Princess.
The Royal Hotel.
Room 1307.
Apologies, my lady. This whole
floor has been reserved.
Did anyone call for this chick?
Who knows?
But I've heard...
that a traitorous scumbag is staying here.
What in the world?!
It's an ambush! A lone woman—
Excuse me.
Vice Minister Brennan from the
auditing department, I presume?
I am terribly sorry if I
interrupted anything...
But may I have the honor
of taking your life?
Code name: Thorn Princess.
An assassin.
She was taught the skills of
her trade from a young age,
and has done any dirty work her
employer requested ever since.
It's not coming off.
Huh? Oh, no! What shall I do?
This is the only nice dress I own.
Now I can't go to the party.
Anyone you're interested in?
It's unheard of to be single at that age.
Make sure you bring your partner with you.
But it's hopeless.
When it comes to homemaking...
Cleaning is the only thing I can do.
Scruffy Head!
I copied all the files of
unmarried women from city hall.
Great, thanks.
You need one who won't care
you're divorced with a kid,
is refined enough for a prestigious school,
and is willing to get married within 48 hours?
If a goddess like that exists,
I'd sure love to meet her.
Meanwhile, I'm not picky at all,
yet I can't even get a date.
How unfortunate.
Don't pity me, asshole!
Is having a kid bad? Am I in the way?
You're not in the way at all.
Don't worry. Just go watch some TV.
'Kay.
Actually, why don't you just use
a female agent from your work?
A lot of them got caught in the recent
spy hunts, so I couldn't find a good match.
Wake up! Hey!
You... You won't get away with this!
Selling people out is really in right now.
We don't have enough agents,
so I got another mission on top of this.
Eliminating a certain smuggling ring.
They're working you to the bone!
Let's just get this over with.
The quickest options would be women in
bad circumstances who'd cooperate with you.
Finding dirt on them might help, too.
If they don't have any,
we can always make some up.
I'd like to avoid anything risky.
Oh, please. She's plenty risky.
She definitely doesn't look like
any princess from a rich family.
Push! Push!
You've got a point.
I need to at least do something
about her appearance.
Now, young lady, I'm going to take
your measurements. Come with me.
I'm being sold off somewhere!
You won't be if you behave.
Honestly, where does she
learn to talk like that?
The seamstress... is married.
The proprietress was listed
among the single women,
but she's been arrested once over
political activities, so she's too dangerous.
Finding the right person
might take longer than—
Pardon me.
Oh, I haven't seen you in a while, Yor.
Hello. I was hoping I could
get my dress fixed up.
Could I get it done as quickly as possible?
But of course. You're one of our regulars.
She managed to slip behind
me so easily. Who is she?
Yor... Yor...
There we go.
Yor Briar, 27 years old.
She has no record of being
married or divorced.
Both of her parents are deceased,
and she has one brother
who's much younger than her.
They're both civil servants
whose records are pretty clean.
Did I just let my guard down?
I'm far too relaxed lately.
Excuse me.
You've been staring at me ever
since I walked in. May I help you?
Impossible! She could even sense my gaze?
Er, no, um, I'm sorry...
I was just admiring how pretty you are.
Does that mean...
You have a favorable impression
of my physical appearance?
Er, well... Yes.
You've got a nice face and body, Yor.
You'd be a knockout if you just dressed up.
Um—
Papa!
I now know how long I am!
Who's that?
Another customer.
He has a child.
I almost pursued someone's husband.
I've heard that women have been
killed by wives for such things.
I mean, if it happened to me,
I'd just kill them back...
Huh?
No, I mustn't.
If I think like this, someone will
eventually figure out that I'm an assassin.
I must learn to be more normal.
A-An assassin?!
A spy... An assassin...
I'm...
so excited!
The little girl was starving
for entertainment.
Hmm... I was considering her as a candidate
to play my wife, but never mind.
I was considering him to act
as my boyfriend at the party,
but I must avoid these so-called
messy lovers' quarrels.
Ah, I am oh so lonely because
I do not have a mama.
What brought this on?
I long for a mama.
Are you not with your wife?
Oh, er...
I actually lost my wife two years ago,
so I'm raising her on my own now.
So I won't be killed for
asking him to the party!
Excuse me...
Pretend to be your boyfriend?
Yes... I fibbed to my younger
brother about having a boyfriend.
If it's not too much trouble, I was
hoping you'd accompany me to this party.
Um, I promise I don't have
any ulterior motives!
Of course, I'll thank you properly, too.
I just want to put my brother's mind at ease.
Very well.
I accept.
Really?!
But I would like something in return.
So you see...
I'd like you to play the role of
her mother during the interview.
Her mother?
With the future being so
uncertain right now,
my only wish is for my daughter
to get into a good school.
This was also the wish of my late wife.
Papa is a liar.
What a wonderful person.
I'll have her accept something simple first,
It will only be one time.
Would you be up for it?
but I'll get her to agree to
a formal marriage in the end.
A-All right... If you think
I'm fit for the role.
Thank you. Then let us reconvene
at Saturday's party.
Yes.
I got a sitter for you on Saturday,
so make sure you behave.
Stock up on them peanuts!
Yeah, yeah.
Ten pents is your change, ribbit.
Thanks, ribbit.
Ribbit?
A T... no, an F cipher.
Must be the details on the extra mission.
Retrieving art pieces that were stolen from
the West and eliminating this smuggling ring.
I'm to carry out this mission Saturday at 1800
hours when the target meets with the buyer.
Saturday?
And so...
We're going to take care of this quickly
so I can make it to the party.
You're helping.
Hang on a second! I'm just an informant!
My fighting skills are literal trash!
Not to mention, you already
pretty much capped your tab—
We're talking 78 art pieces valued
at a total of three million dalcs.
I'm almost certain no one would notice
if one or two happened to go missing.
Leave it to me.
I just so happen to have invented some
new spy gear just for days like this.
He's so useful.
Loid is awfully late.
I hope he wasn't in some terrible accident.
Hold it!
Who're you workin' for?!
You didn't tell me there'd
be an army of them!
Two, four, six... 38 of them.
I can't afford to waste even
ten seconds on each one!
Reinforcements! There's no end to them.
I got 'em all in! Get in!
Whoo!
Let's see... Which one's going
to accidentally go missing?
I'm helping myself to this one.
Hey, that's a diamond! No fair
taking the expensive-looking one!
I'll use it as part of this whole charade.
Shut up! Give that back!
I see.
So this is what it means to
have your heart toyed with.
I must keep my work relationships
favorable for my brother's sake, too.
Which means that I must attend this party.
You're late, Yor!
I do apologize. Here's a gift.
Oh? I thought you were
coming with your boyfriend.
Unfortunately, he had something
suddenly come up.
Oh, what a shame. I was so eager to meet him!
What a lame excuse.
How pathetic.
I knew she was lying about having a guy.
Should we report the liar?
We should!
I'm positive she's a spy who's been sent
in to lower our country's birth rate.
Seriously? That's so petty.
She's just unpopular with the guys.
Just leave her be.
You're meaner than both of us, Sharon.
It's too bad your boyfriend couldn't
make it. I was excited to meet him.
You're so hilarious.
D-Dominic...
Yuri's always so worried about you.
Um, could you possibly...
just tell my brother than I came
to the party with a kind gentleman?
Yeah, not happening.
Just how desperate are you
to impress people, Yor?
It just makes you look even more pathetic.
Jeez, knock it off, Camilla!
Stop talking to my man.
I'll be sure to let your brother
know that you came alone.
What could she possibly gain by doing that?
This is honestly becoming tiresome.
If all of the adults here
just happened to perish,
my brother would never find out...
I'm so sorry. Have fun!
Come on, Camilla. Help me bake this gratin.
And then that guy...
Mommy!
My oldest here will be taking
an entrance exam soon.
At the prestigious Eden College.
Wow, that's wonderful!
He'll be a shoe-in with the elite.
That must be what "normal" looks like.
I'm sure that's how my
brother wanted me to end up.
Seriously? She's still here.
She's tougher than she looks.
I'm honestly surprised she had
the nerve to show up alone.
I see... I'm too out of my league here.
I do beg your pardon.
I will have to take my leav—
I'm terribly sorry for arriving late.
I'm Yor's husband, Loid Forger.
Um...
I just needed a boyfriend, not a husband.
Shit!
I mixed up my mission with hers.
Um... Mr. Forger, was it? You're bleeding.
Oh, pardon me.
One of my patients had a violent episode.
It happens all the time to a psychiatrist.
Have you been enjoying yourself, Yor?
You're joking, right?
You're married, Yor?
Why didn't you tell us?
Um, I...
It's embarrassing to say so, but this is my
second marriage and I already have a child,
so it may have been hard to bring up.
Don't give me that shit!
It's my fault.
There's absolutely no way Yor has a
husband who's that handsome and hot!
I'll embarrass her in front of everyone!
Yor, I just got this piping hot
gratin right out of the oven!
Oops, I seemed to have tripped!
I admire your dedication to not wasting food,
but it's a bit improper
to use your feet, Yor.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
That got you?
This is quite delicious.
Indeed.
Did you know, Mr. Ranger...
It's Forger.
...that she was apparently doing some
questionable work before working at city hall?
What did you do again?
Come on, stop it!
Men would call you to their hotel rooms
so you could give them "massages"?
Oh, you little whore.
That was...
"Massages" were a cover
for occupational murders.
Um, please don't get the
wrong idea, Loid. I—
How wonderful.
Huh?
Yor lost her parents at a very young age.
She did all she could to care
for her younger brother,
even if it meant sacrificing herself.
Be it for someone else
or for a specific reason,
having to endure a merciless job
requires an incredible amount of dedication.
And that's something to be very proud of.
Let's go home, Yor.
Er, yes... Thank you for
the lovely party, everyone.
I-I'm so sorry I said I was your husband.
Oh, it's all right.
I'm not sure what to tell your
brother if he hears of this.
Um, Loid... I have a suggestion.
What...
Remnants of the smuggling ring?
Hang on, Yor!
Huh?
How did they know where I was?
Did they... leave a tracking
device in the art pieces?
You've definitely let your
guard down, Twilight.
Who are those people?
Um, uh...
I-It appears some of my
patients still haven't recovered
from their psychotic episodes.
Being a doctor must be very taxing.
She actually believed it!
In the meantime...
We're making a break for it.
They've abandoned the van.
They're probably hiding nearby.
Split up and find them.
Yor, this way. Hurry!
Um... Are you sure it's all right for
you to hit your patients like that?
Um, well...
The concussive recovery method is the
latest in modern medical practices.
I see.
This is fiction.
I can't tell if she's
actually bright or dumb.
Look out, Yor!
Another one! I can't dodge it!
Oh, no!
I'm so sorry an amateur like me
helped with the recovery!
I happen to be an expert in self-defense.
My brother was kind enough to teach me...
Thank you, Yor.
That was quite impressive.
Did you see how far he went?
I'm sorry. I guess I did send him flying.
There he is!
This way!
Do whatever you need to do!
Make sure they're dead!
Um, Loid... This may not
be the best moment to ask,
but why don't we get married?
I'm sorry?!
Er, well, it would extend our agreement...
I mean... Apparently, I'm considered
suspicious just for being single,
so it'd be nice camouflage...
For me to continue my job
as an assassin, too.
Um, basically,
if it's all right with you,
maybe we could just stay together,
and not just for the interview...
For both our sakes.
He's probably the only person who could
accept me for who I am right now.
Then let's stop by city hall on our
way back to fill out the paperwork.
Huh? Right now?!
They do say no time like the present.
Oh, that's right.
Where did I drop it?
You bastard!
We have 'em cornered!
Fill 'em full of lead!
Yor...
Even in sickness,
or in sadness...
No matter what hardships await us,
let us be there for one another.
All right.
Until my mission...
Until my killing...
...do us part.
PREPARE FOR THE INTERVIEW